{
  "allQuestions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of these films was Hema Malini's directorial debut in Bollywood?",
      "answer": [
        "Jugnu",
        "Dil Aashna Hai",
        "Lal Patthar",
        "Sholay"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Dil Aashna Hai"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of Sholay' s iconic villain?",
      "answer": [
        "Shakaal",
        "Gabar",
        "Kaancha",
        "Kalia"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Gabar"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Jab We Met, what is the name of Geet's first love?",
      "answer": [
        "Aakash",
        "Aakash",
        "Anshuman",
        "Avirudh"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Anshuman"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Chak De! India, how many minutes, according to coach Kabir Khan, does the team have?",
      "answer": [
        "90",
        "45",
        "30",
        "70"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "70"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Chak De! India, how many minutes, according to coach Kabir Khan, does the team have?",
      "answer": [
        "Chatur Ramalingam",
        "Phunsukh Wangdu",
        "Ranchhoddas Shamaldas Chanchad",
        "Viru Sahastrabuddhe"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Phunsukh Wangdu"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the lead female character in Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge?",
      "answer": [
        "Simran",
        "Pooja",
        "Senorita",
        "Sunita"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Simran"
    },
    {
      "question": "Finish the quote from Deewar: \"Mere paas _____.\"",
      "answer": [
        "Ghar Hai",
        "Paisa Hai",
        "Baap Hai",
        "Maa Hai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Maa Hai"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Karthik Calling Karthik, who was actually calling Karthik?",
      "answer": [
        "Karthik",
        "Ravi",
        "Kiran",
        "Kunal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Karthik"
    },
    {
      "question": "In Om Shanti Om, what does Deepika Padukone's character Shantipriya do?",
      "answer": [
        "Journalist",
        "Actress",
        "Singer",
        "Lawyer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Actress"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which cities does Rani visit when she goes on her 'solo' honeymoon in Queen?",
      "answer": [
        "Londan and New York",
        "Paris and London",
        "Paris and Amsterdam",
        "Tokyo and Shanghai"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Paris and Amsterdam"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Bunny's real name, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "Kabir Singh",
        "Kabir Gupta",
        "Kabir Thapar",
        "Kabir Agrawal"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kabir Thapar"
    },{
      "question": "What game do they play on the train, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani??",
      "answer": [
        "Hide and Seek",
        "Truth and Dare",
        "Antakshari",
        "Never Have I Ever"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Never Have I Ever"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Avi's full name, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "Aditya Roy Kapur",
        "Avinash Shiv",
        "Avram Mukherjee",
        "Avinash Choudhary"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Avinash Shiv"
    },
    {
      "question": "What kind of dog does Naina have, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "Golden Retriever",
        "Pug",
        "Chihuahua",
        "Labrador"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Pug"
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the name of Madhuri Dixit's character, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "Mohini",
        "Munni",
        "Sheela",
        "Sohini"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Mohini"
    },
    {
      "question": "What song do Bunny and Avi wake Aditi with, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "Ek Chumma to mujhko udhaar de de",
        "Jumma Chumma De De",
        "Chahe Koi Mujhe Junglee Kahe",
        "Yeh Mera Dil"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Jumma Chumma De De"
    },
    {
      "question": "When climbing up to the Bhairav Mandir, what alcohol does Bunny give Naina, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "Naina doesn't drink!",
        "Whiskey",
        "Lugdi",
        "Old Monk"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Lugdi"
    },
    {
      "question": "What animal did Naina and Bunny spot on the hill, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "A Lion",
        "A Bear",
        "A Tiger",
        "A Deer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "A Deer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What college did Bunny get accepted to, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "Northwestern University",
        "University of Chicago",
        "Stanford University",
        "Columbia University"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Northwestern University"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where in the world is Aditi's wedding, Yeh Jawaani hai Deewani?",
      "answer": [
        "Delhi",
        "Udaipur",
        "Jaipur",
        "Jodhpur"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Udaipur"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nayak launch on?",
      "answer": [
        "2004",
        "2001",
        "2000",
        "2002"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2001"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lakshya launch on?",
      "answer": [
        "2004",
        "2002",
        "2003",
        "2001"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2004"
    },
    {
      "question": "3 idiots launch date?",
      "answer": [
        "2014",
        "2009",
        "2011",
        "2010"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2009"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lagaan launch date?",
      "answer": [
        "2002",
        "2001",
        "2005",
        "2009"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2002"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mother India launch date?",
      "answer": [
        "1955",
        "1958",
        "1960",
        "1949"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "1958"
    },
    {
      "question": "Saaho launch date?",
      "answer": [
        "2018",
        "2016",
        "2021",
        "2019"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gandhi launch date?",
      "answer": [
        "1985",
        "1980",
        "1983",
        "1987"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "1983"
    },
    {
      "question": "War launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2018",
        "2017",
        "2020",
        "2019"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mission Mangal launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2019",
        "2018",
        "2015",
        "2016"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Housefull 4 launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2019",
        "2016",
        "2021",
        "2020"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dabangg 3 launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2016",
        "2019",
        "2015",
        "2020"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Gully Boy launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2020",
        "2019",
        "2021",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Good Newwz launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2018",
        "2016",
        "2019",
        "2021"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bharat launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2019",
        "2020",
        "2021",
        "2018"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Uri: The Surgical Strike launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2020",
        "2016",
        "2017",
        "2019"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2019"
    },
    {
      "question": "Krrish 3 launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2011",
        "2013",
        "2016",
        "2012"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2013"
    },
    {
      "question": "Raanjhanaa launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2010",
        "2013",
        "2012",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2013"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yeh Jawaani Hai Deewani launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2015",
        "2018",
        "2013",
        "2019"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2013"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bhaag Milkha Bhaag launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2013",
        "2018",
        "2016",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2013"
    },
    {
      "question": "Race 2 launched on?",
      "answer": [
        "2009",
        "2010",
        "2013",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2013"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dhoom 3 launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2013",
        "2014",
        "2016",
        "2010"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2013"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dilwale launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2010",
        "2015",
        "2016",
        "2014"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bajrangi Bhaijaan launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2015",
        "2014",
        "2016",
        "2013"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Prem Ratan Dhan Payo launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2018",
        "2016",
        "2017",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Bajirao Mastani launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2015",
        "2016",
        "2018",
        "2010"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Welcome Back launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2020",
        "2018",
        "2015",
        "2016"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "ABCD 2 launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2014",
        "2013",
        "2012",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dil Dhadakne Do launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2017",
        "2016",
        "2010",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Baby launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2015",
        "2014",
        "2016",
        "2018"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Roy launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2015",
        "2016",
        "2018",
        "2016"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "NH10 launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2016",
        "2018",
        "2015",
        "2014"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Piku launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2016",
        "2018",
        "2015",
        "2014"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Drishyam launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2013",
        "2015",
        "2017",
        "2018"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Singh Is Bliing launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2014",
        "2017",
        "2013",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Talvar launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2018",
        "2016",
        "2014",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hate Story 3 launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2014",
        "2015",
        "2016",
        "2013"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kis Kisko Pyaar Karoon launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2014",
        "2016",
        "2018",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kis Kisko Pyaar Karoon launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2014",
        "2016",
        "2018",
        "2015"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2015"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dabangg launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2011",
        "2009",
        "2010",
        "2012"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2010"
    },
    {
      "question": "Veer launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2013",
        "2014",
        "2015",
        "2010"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2010"
    },
    {
      "question": "Golmaal 3 launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2010",
        "2015",
        "2014",
        "2012"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2010"
    },
    {
      "question": "Raajneeti launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2015",
        "2010",
        "2012",
        "2011"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2010"
    },
    {
      "question": "Raavan launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2012",
        "2014",
        "2010",
        "2013"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2010"
    },
    {
      "question": "Tees Maar Khan launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2012",
        "2013",
        "2014",
        "2010"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2010"
    },
    {
      "question": "Once Upon A Time In Mumbaai launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2010",
        "2014",
        "2011",
        "2012"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2010"
    },
    {
      "question": "Anjaana Anjaani launched at?",
      "answer": [
        "2011",
        "2010",
        "2009",
        "2008"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2010"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Lucky Singh’s assistant’s name in Lage Raho Munna Bhai?",
      "answer": [
        "Kuku",
        "Gujju",
        "Munna",
        "Circuit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kuku"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the radio station Jhanvi works at, in Lage Raho Munna Bhai?",
      "answer": [
        "102.6 RADIO MUMBAI",
        "World Space Radio",
        "Radio City",
        "93.5 Red FM"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "World Space Radio"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many senior citizens live at the Second Innings House, in Lage Raho Munna Bhai?",
      "answer": [
        "4",
        "6",
        "7",
        "5"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Lucky Singh’s official name, in Lage Raho Munna Bhai?",
      "answer": [
        "Mohan Singh",
        "Lakhan Singh",
        "Milkha Singh",
        "Laal Singh"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Lakhan Singh"
    },
    {
      "question": "What flowers do the Kkhuranas consider unlucky, in Lage Raho Munna Bhai?",
      "answer": [
        "Rose",
        "Mogra",
        "Jasmine",
        "Lilly"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Rose"
    },
    {
      "question": "who say “Uth re tereko sorry bolne ka hai.”, in Lage Raho Munna Bhai?",
      "answer": [
        "Lucky",
        "Baapu",
        "Munna",
        "Circuit"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Circuit"
    },
    {
      "question": "The first song to play in the film in Lagaan?",
      "answer": [
        "Radha kaise na jale",
        "O re Chori",
        "Ghanan Ghanan",
        "Mitwa"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Ghanan Ghanan"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is the story set, in Lagaan?",
      "answer": [
        "Champaner Village",
        "Khavda Village",
        "Ramghar Village",
        "Bhuj Village"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Champaner Village"
    },
    {
      "question": "What’s the name of the king of the village, in Lagaan?",
      "answer": [
        "Surya Pratap Singh",
        "Rajdeep Singh Chawla",
        "Puran Singh Chawla",
        "Uday Singh Chawla"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Puran Singh Chawla"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who’s the spinner in Bhuvan’s team, in Lagaan?",
      "answer": [
        "Lakha",
        "Kachra",
        "Guran",
        "Bhuvan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Kachra"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who has a clumsy hand while fielding, in Lagaan?",
      "answer": [
        "Bhura",
        "Guran",
        "Bagha",
        "Lakha"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Bagha"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who takes a hattrick from Bhuvan’s team, in Lagaan?",
      "answer": [
        "Lakha",
        "Kachra",
        "Shibu",
        "Bhuvan"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Sister"
    },
    {
      "question": "By what nickname does Amrish Puri call Farida Jalal in DDLJ?",
      "answer": [
        "Lajjo",
        "Piyo",
        "Ladho",
        "Raani"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Lajjo"
    },
    {
      "question": "In which area of London does Raj stay in DDLJ?",
      "answer": [
        "Hampsted",
        "Hampton",
        "Ickenham",
        "Canary Wharf"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Hampsted"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Rajesh’s hobby in Hum Aapke Hain Koun?",
      "answer": [
        "Poetry",
        "Painting",
        "Dancing",
        "Singing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Painting"
    }    
  ]
}


